Bed 16.
السرير رقم 16.
Well,
حسنًا،
you
أنت
should be careful.
ينبغي توخي الحذر.
Let me know
اسمحوا لي أن أعرف
when you get home.
عندما تصل إلى المنزل.
What do you want to eat tomorrow?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل غداً؟
I want
أريد
Hunan cuisine.
مطبخ هونان.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll pick you up after work tomorrow.
سآتي لأخذك بعد العمل غداً.
Actually, I think that...
في الحقيقة، أعتقد أن...
Mengmeng.
منغمنغ.
Hello, Mengmeng.
مرحبا، منغ مينغ.
Long time no see.
وقت طويل لا رؤية.
My dear brother,
أخي العزيز،
Lin Mojiao.
لين موجياو.
Where is Xu Meng?
أين شو مينغ؟
What did you do to her?
ماذا فعلت بها؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Mobilize everyone
حشد الجميع
until Xu Meng is found.
إلى أن يتم العثور على شو مينغ.
Meng,
مينغ،
where are you?
أين أنت؟
Hello,
مرحبًا،
did you sleep well last night?
هل نمت جيداً الليلة الماضية؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
If you want to see Xu Meng,
إذا كنت ترغب في رؤية شو مينغ،
come alone.
تعال بمفردك.
Don't play tricks.
لا تمارس الخدع.
Does this place look familiar?
هل يبدو هذا المكان مألوفاً؟
Meng,
مينغ،
I advise you not to act rashly.
أنصحك بعدم التصرف بتهور.
You want me,
أنت تريدني،
She has nothing to do with this.
ليس لها أي علاقة بهذا الأمر.
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You and her...
أنت وهي...
I won't let either of you go.
لن أدع أيًا منكما يذهب.
Lin Mojiao,
لين موجياو,
why are you doing this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
Ever since you joined the Lin family,
منذ انضمامك إلى عائلة لين،
you've been making my life difficult.
لقد جعلت حياتي صعبة.
It's all because of you.
كل ذلك بفضلك.
You took everything from me.
لقد أخذت كل شيء مني.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why should I grow up
لماذا عليّ أن أكبر؟
in such a repressed environment?
في مثل هذه البيئة القمعية؟
You can have all the love of your parents.
يمكنك أن تنال كل حب والديك.
So you killed your mom
إذن أنت قتلت أمك
to get into the Lin family?
للدخول إلى عائلة لين؟
I didn't kill her.
لم أقتلها.
She sacrificed herself for me willingly.
لقد ضحت بنفسها من أجلي عن طيب خاطر.
What about my mom?
وماذا عن أمي؟
She took you in out of kindness.
لقد استقبلتك بدافع اللطف.
Why did you kill her?
لماذا قتلتها؟
Kindness?
العطف؟
I've been living in your house,
لقد كنت أعيش في منزلك،
serving you,
في خدمتكم،
and living a dependent life.
والعيش حياةً تعتمد على الآخرين.
We never asked you to do these.
لم نطلب منك أبدًا القيام بهذه الأمور.
You think
كنت أعتقد
it's because you're narrow-minded,
ذلك لأنك ضيق الأفق،
thinking we look down on you.
نظن أننا ننظر إليكم بازدراء.
That's because you
ذلك لأنك
never treated me as
لم يعاملني أبداً كـ
a member of the Lin family.
أحد أفراد عائلة لين.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I...
أنا...
I'm here to bring you tea.
أنا هنا لأحضر لكم الشاي.
This is a confidential file of Lin Group.
هذا ملف سري خاص بمجموعة لين.
You can't read it casually.
لا يمكنك قراءته بشكل عابر.
If you do it again,
إذا فعلت ذلك مرة أخرى،
I'll send you abroad.
سأرسلك إلى الخارج.
I just
أنا فقط
took a glance at the file that day.
ألقيت نظرة سريعة على الملف في ذلك اليوم.
Your mother wanted to kick me out of the Lin family.
أرادت والدتك طردي من عائلة لين.
She never treated me as a family member.
لم تعاملني قط كفرد من أفراد عائلتها.
So
لذا
you killed her?
هل قتلتها؟
Your mother has long suspected me.
لطالما شكت والدتك بي.
If I didn't kill her,
لو لم أقتلها،
Lin Huaiwang would never give me anything.
لن يعطيني لين هوايوانغ أي شيء على الإطلاق.
Everything about the Lin family has nothing to do with me.
لا علاقة لي بأي شيء يتعلق بعائلة لين.
But Lin Huaiwang perjured for you,
لكن لين هوايوانغ شهد زوراً من أجلك،
saying my mother died by accident.
أقول إن والدتي ماتت في حادث.
That old bastard!
ذلك الوغد العجوز!
That old bastard should have died long ago!
كان ينبغي أن يموت ذلك الوغد العجوز منذ زمن طويل!
Damn it!
عليك اللعنة!
Mo Jiao.
مو جياو.
Give me the document.
أعطني الوثيقة.
Fifty percent?
خمسون بالمئة؟
Why should he take half of my shares?
لماذا يجب أن يأخذ نصف حصتي؟
He's your brother.
إنه أخوك.
Besides,
بجانب،
without his mother,
بدون والدته،
there wouldn't be the Lin Group today.
لم تكن مجموعة لين لتوجد اليوم.
Dad,
أب،
I was just kidding.
كنت أمزح فقط.
I will definitely share these shares
سأشارك هذه المشاركات بالتأكيد
equally with my brother.
وكذلك أخي.
It's time to take your medicine. Dad,
حان وقت تناول دوائك يا أبي .
He kept mentioning your name until his last breath.
ظل يذكر اسمك حتى أنفاسه الأخيرة.
Do you know that?
هل تعلم ذلك؟
I'm his only son!
أنا ابنه الوحيد!
Why do you have everything?
لماذا تملك كل شيء؟
If you hadn't shown up,
لو لم تحضر،
everything would be mine.
كل شيء سيكون ملكي.
Lin Group,
مجموعة لين،
Blue Crane,
بلو كرين،
Zhu Rong, all of these
تشو رونغ، كل هؤلاء
should have been mine!
كان يجب أن يكون لي!
Mine.
مِلكِي.
No.
لا.
They are all mine.
جميعها ملكي.
You also think they are all mine, right?
أنت تعتقد أيضاً أنها جميعاً ملكي، أليس كذلك؟
I also think they are all mine.
أعتقد أيضاً أنها جميعها ملكي.
Mo Jiao.
مو جياو.
Come to me.
تعالى لي.
Mojiao.
موجياو.
Come.
يأتي.
Everything of Dad's is yours.
كل ما يملكه أبي هو ملكك.
Come quickly, Mojiao.
تعالي بسرعة يا موجياو.
Come on.
تعال.
Mojiao.
موجياو.
Come.
يأتي.
It's all yours.
كل شيء لك.
It's all mine.
كل شيء ملكي.
Right.
يمين.
It's all yours.
كل شيء لك.
Everything of Dad's is yours.
كل ما يملكه أبي هو ملكك.
Come here. Mojiao.
تعال إلى هنا. موجياو.
Come to me.
تعالى لي.
Come.
يأتي.
Mojiao.
موجياو.
I'm waiting for you here.
أنا أنتظرك هنا.
Mojiao, come here.
موجياو، تعال إلى هنا.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
It's all mine.
كل شيء ملكي.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
I'm going to work.
سأذهب إلى العمل.
Sleep a bit more.
نم قليلاً أكثر.
I have a meeting this morning.
لدي اجتماع هذا الصباح.
I'm in your bed.
أنا في سريرك.
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Really?
حقًا؟
I can't do anything about you.
لا أستطيع فعل أي شيء حيالك.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
This one needs to be roasted a bit more.
هذا يحتاج إلى تحميص أكثر قليلاً.
Okay.
تمام.
but not overcooked. No problem.
لكن ليس مطبوخاً أكثر من اللازم. لا مشكلة.
Why are you out again?
لماذا أنت بالخارج مرة أخرى؟
The doctor told you to rest more.
نصحك الطبيب بالراحة أكثر.
You love it.
أنت تحبه.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
I'll call the doctor.
سأتصل بالطبيب.
No need.
لا حاجة.
The baby is kicking me.
الطفل يركلني.
The baby is really moving.
الطفل يتحرك كثيراً.
So energetic. I don't know who it takes after.
مفعم بالحيوية. لا أعرف من ورث هذه الحيوية.
Like you.
مثلك.
Take a picture for me.
التقط لي صورة.
Okay.
تمام.
Pretty.
جميل.
When will it be ready?
متى سيكون جاهزاً؟
I'm so hungry.
أنا جائع جداً.
Here.
هنا.
Not bad.
ليس سيئًا.
Is it tasty?
هل هو حسن الطعم ؟
Needs more salt.
يحتاج إلى المزيد من الملح.
How's that?
كيف ذلك؟
What are you taking pictures of?
ما الذي تقوم بتصويره؟
Don't put so much.
لا تضع الكثير.
I'll try again.
سأحاول مرة أخرى.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I'll ask Mengmeng to take it for me.
سأطلب من مينغمينغ أن تأخذه نيابة عني.
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
Coming.
آت.
Here. Eat it while it's hot.
تفضل. تناوله وهو ساخن.
I want to eat this.
أريد أن آكل هذا.
Crabs are cold in nature.
السرطانات حيوانات باردة بطبيعتها.
You can't eat it.
لا يمكنك أكله.
It's not me who wants to eat it.
أنا لست من يريد أكله.
It's the baby in my belly who wants to eat it.
الطفل الذي في بطني هو من يريد أن يأكله.
Eat this. You can eat this.
تناول هذا. يمكنك تناول هذا.
Fine.
بخير.
Wenjie,
وينجي،
you've become so picky now.
لقد أصبحتَ شديد الانتقائية الآن.
Why don't you name your baby
لماذا لا تسمي طفلك؟
Chanchan?
شانشان؟
Chanchan.
شانشان.
I think it's good.
أعتقد أنه أمر جيد.
Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
what should we name our baby?
ماذا نسمي طفلنا؟
If it's a boy,
إذا كان ولداً،
we can name it Lianqing.
يمكننا تسميتها ليانكينغ.
If it's a girl,
إذا كانت فتاة،
we can name it Qingmeng. How do you like it?
يمكننا تسميتها تشينغمينغ. ما رأيك؟
So old-fashioned. Old-fashioned?
قديم الطراز. قديم الطراز؟
You're so shameless.
أنت عديم الحياء.
You haven't even asked me to marry you.
لم تطلب مني الزواج حتى الآن.
Yeah.
نعم.
You haven't even asked her to marry you.
لم تطلب منها الزواج حتى.
I'm preparing for it.
أنا أستعد لذلك.
Okay? Come on.
حسناً؟ هيا.
Let's toast
فلنحتفل
to Lianqing, Qingmeng,
إلى ليانتشينغ، تشينغمينغ
and Chanchan.
وتشانشان.
Cheers.
هتافات.
Drink it up.
اشربها.